

Toulouse, France

coumbaseck17@icloud.com

+33 7 83 58 40 86

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

Portfolio

EDUCATION

 Master's in Computer Sciences and Project Management 2022-2024).

Data and Security track

- Toulouse III Paul Sabatier University
- Bachelor's in Computer Sciences and Project Management (2019-2022)
 - Toulouse III Paul Sabatier University

LANGUAGES

French: Advanced

English: Advanced

Italian: Native Language

Coumba Seck

DATA ANALYST

SUMMARY

About to graduate with a Master's degree in Computer Science and Project Management, I am actively seeking new career opportunities starting from October. With two years of experience gained through internships, I have developed strong skills in data analysis, software development, and project management. I am determined to apply these skills to the success of projects focused on intelligent data utilization.

EXPERIENCE

Sopra Steria

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

September 2022 - August 2024

- Development and integration of RESTful APIs
- Development of user interfaces
- Implementation of complex business logic
- Close collaboration with project team members.

Orange Business Services

PRODUCTION TOOLS DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP April 2022 - August 2022

- Design and development of an automation system for processing production requests
- Collaboration with internal stakeholders to understand and gather requirements
- Implémentation de logique métier et de règles de traitement dans les scripts d'automatisationImplementation of business logic and processing rules in automation scripts.

PROJETS

WASABI DATAVIZ

- Data visualization with a music API
 - o Data processing with Python
 - o Frontend development with Vue.js
 - o Implementation of charts with D3.js

MIAGE LAND

- Development of an amusement park management application
 - o Spring Boot for backend application development
 - o Frontend development with Vue.js

SKILLS

- Programming languages: SQL, NoSQL, Python, Javascript, HTML, Java. C
- Frameworks: Hadoop, Angular, Vue.js, ReactJS, Spring Boot
- Database Management: mySQL, MongoDB, Neo4j, DynamoDB
- Softwares: Power BI, Keycloak